I'm really tired of the coddling of Jewish folks.
People who are claiming to be your people
have been wreaking havoc for quite some time.
Yeah, for quite some time.
Yes, there was a Holocaust.
It was one of many, by the way.
There are entire communities right now in the United States
that have been gutted by folks who are aligned
and members of the Jewish faith
and have done so under the auspices of,
I'm Jewish, I can do that.
Entire countries being gutted
and folks are wearing their yarmulke to the mines
where they're watching people and children die for their riches.
I don't think it's our responsibility to yell louder
that not Jews are all the same.
I expect the high quality whites to say,
ah, ah, ah, I am not them.
Here's my resistance resume.
I expect the Christians who are actually
living in Christ consciousness to say,
oh, oh, oh, I'm not them folks
who are taking away all your rights.
Not me.
Yeah.
This whole, you're anti-Semitic,
if you call out Judaism as a problematic space,
them days are done.
Because too many folks have hidden behind
the veil of Judaism
in order to carry out the wreaking of havoc.
Because see, what a lot of people don't realize
is that when people are calling out anti-Semitism,
et cetera, et cetera,
they're not trying to protect Judaism.
They're not trying to protect Jews.
They're trying to protect Zionism,
which is supremacy.
And as far as I'm concerned,
I have no interest in protecting anybody
who's trying to protect that.
And as far as I'm concerned,
I'm not trying to protect them.
I'm trying to protect them.